Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, but so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We live in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Orchaka!
Terrible news! It's the king!
What do you mean?
What's happened to his majesty?
He's disappeared!
That's absurd!
Have you searched everywhere? Yes!
We searched the palace, the
garden, and the storehouses!
Could he have slipped away
in the middle of the night?
Impossible!
The king's security was airtight!
There's no way he could
have gotten past us!
But why?
Why would the king hide
himself just before the battle?
Search!
Check outside the palace and in the town!
Sir!
If only Pell were here instead of
on reconnaissance and rain base,
he excels at tracking people.
What could have happened to his majesty?
I can't afford to act recklessly.
Damn it!
Lord Chaka, we have news
of the King! What is it?
Have you found him? Yes, sir.
He's in Nanohana.
The information is certain.
Good. That's a relief.
Yes, but...
Well, sir, you see, it's not that simple.
What is it?
Why now, all of a sudden?
Has he fallen as far as he can?
Don't be so suspicious, Koza.
Why would he do something this crazy?
Koza.
You know his majesty's
character too well for that.
He would never betray us.
That's what all you old people say.
I didn't come all the
way to you, but with you.
Just to please the king.
The rebels were over a
hundred thousand strong now.
Yes, I've heard.
And there have been casualties, too.
It's nothing.
A little rain and these suspicions
will vanish like fog. Yes.
What?
The canal's been destroyed.
Who would do this?
Now, we can't bring water to the town.
It hasn't rained for over a year.
Aramalu is done for.
Don't be so suspicious, Koza.
I don't want to suspect you,
but people are dying of thirst.
Maybe you're not using
it, but you do have it.
No.
We must wait for natural rain.
To use dance powder is
to summon misfortune.
Just a small amount should be all right.
The rebellion might stop even
if there's just a little rain.
It would only result in
an even greater calamity.
I understand your desperation, but
it's not as easy as you think, Koza.
I can't stand to watch
towns dry up anymore!
I've got to do something!
You haven't changed a bit
from the old days, have you?
Yes, I have.
Now I can fight.
And I swear, I'll come back here.
And when I do, I'm going to
take your reign from you.
Jai, you mean...
What was that?
You heard me right.
I've come here to apologize to you all.
It was none other than I, the ruler of
Alabasta, who stole all this country's reign.
My lord, surely you must be
joking with us. You must be.
I'm not joking.
You're mad.
You knew how desperate things were
and yet you only helped yourself.
No decent ruler would be so selfish if
he knew his own people were in need.
How dare you, a common peasant, speak
disrespectfully to your lord and master.
Even though I needn't
justify my actions to you,
I came to Nanohana to
apologize for what I've done.
What more do you want?
My brother died in Yuba thanks to you.
I didn't come all the way to
this town just to apologize.
There is another reason.
As you may know, Dance Powder is
outlawed by the world government.
If word got out that
it had been used here,
the marines would certainly take
action and destroy this country.
I cannot allow that.
You may also remember that
large amounts of dance powder
were found being smuggled out
of this town two years ago.
It is necessary to eliminate
all traces of that incident.
Do I make myself clear?
You mean...
I do.
There is only one way to erase
this incident from our past.
We must obliterate Nanohana
and everyone in it!
We have to die because
you're going to win?
That's insane!
Hey, King!
So it was all your fault after all! You...
you stole the rain and killed the towns!
I'll get even with you
for what you've done!
I'll make you pay for this.
Apple, are you all right?
Please, no.
Men, burn it to the ground
and leave no one alive.
Koza, it's Koza.
Koza, it's been a while.
What are you doing?
What I'm apologizing.
I thought I had made that
clear. Shut up! Just shut up!
Do you have any idea what you're doing
to the people who believed in you?
It is an insult.
Nevertheless, I am the one
who's been using dance powder.
I told you to shut up.
Why are you so angry? Kohza?
Surely even you behind us.
What I'm trying to do...
You cold, heartless bastard!
Don't...
Don't you understand?
Don't you know how these people
felt as they died of thirst?
They felt no hatred or anger towards you!
It isn't the king's fault this is
happening to us, he's a great leader!
Those were the words on their lips as
they died, they never lost faith in you!
But now, you come here and apologize,
and what happens to their faith?
At least have the decency to
lie and say you're innocent!
Who's the leader?
Okay, kids, let's go!
Didn't we fight?
Because the kingdom, because everyone,
wanted to know if you were innocent.
At the very least
That's why I fought
I don't believe it
Showtime!
A giant ship's about to crash!
What kind of ship is that?
It's only over!
For the big finale, that was sure easy.
Have we ever done
anything that wasn't easy?
We pulled it off!
Now, let's light the
fires and get out of here!
It feels so good to get back into gear!
Koza, say something, Koza! Come on!
Look, the royal army has disappeared!
What?
Was I the kingliest king you ever
saw back there, or was I not?
Yes, you were the
greatest, Mr. Barclay, sir!
Stop those fires!
The Royal Army started
the fires, then ran off!
Hurry!
We've got to put them out!
Now all we have to do is meet up with Mr.
Two outside town.
Alabarna's the grand climax.
Hmm.
Frankly, I'm looking forward to it.
You know my favorite word is vague.
I love that word.
The king's prospects of staying
king are exceedingly vague.
The operation is a success.
Where's Moochie?
He's west of town, Mr.
Toubon Clay, sir.
What the the king turned into
some kind of weird ballerina.
It's no use we can't stop him!
He wasn't the king.
This is bad everyone's been
tricked i have to tell them.
What a naughty boy how
much do you think he knows?
That imbecile he had to
get careless and screw up.
Who are you?
I don't suppose you'd stay
quiet if we asked you.
Water!
We need more water!
Wait!
That's my water!
Can't you pay for it?
Not now, you idiot!
The town's on fire!
Put out the fire!
Useless.
It's just burning too quickly.
We should escape while we still can.
Don't give up yet, Koza.
You're not the type to just
give in and die like this.
You gotta fight!
What?
Here, take Koza.
Hey, kid, say something. Damn.
Even children aren't safe.
What?
Don't try and talk, kid. I've gotcha.
It's not what you think.
Everyone's been tricked.
Hang in there, son.
Koza.
This country must die.
Contact all of our units.
This will be our final battle!
Well, all right, but we still
don't have enough weapons.
No, we have plenty.
Now you know that ship that
just crashed into town?
As fate would have it,
it's an armory ship.
Wait, are you sure?
Yeah, it's full of weapons.
It's almost like...
divine guidance.
Really?
Some little pipsqueak saw me?
Well, excuse me, so sorry!
Shut up.
Now all that remains is for Mr.
Forest Team to do its thing.
Fatty and that old hag know
how to get things done.
Catching the king will
be a snap, you'll see!
Oh, joy! I can't wait!
Hear me, rebel army!
The Alabasta of old is dead now!
This will be our ultimate battle!
We go now to capture the capital!
Onward!
To Alubarna!
The king must play!
We'll build a new country!
That's absurd!
Lord Cobra would never do
anything as mad as that!
It must be a mistake! It's
true! And what's more,
the timing between his
disappearance from the
palace and his appearance
at Nanohana fits perfectly.
Excuses are useless now.
News of the Nanohana incident
has spread throughout
Alabasta and rebel soldiers
everywhere are responding.
Even worse,
citizens who once had faith in the king
are now taking up arms against him.
They're on their way here.
The entire kingdom is
rising up in rebellion.
We have to act.
My lord, please command us.
Whatever you decide, we will obey you.
How can this be?
Even the king's words from
yesterday seem blurred now.
What can I depend on?
Very well.
We have no choice but to
perform our sworn duty.
We are the royal guards of Alabasta.
We cannot let the kingdom crumble to
the ground in the absence of the king.
Fulfill your oath!
Defend the truth before you!
We must stop the rebel army!
That's horrifying!
Well, do you like it?
The operation you once participated
in is now reaching fruition
If you listen closely, I wager you
can hear the howls of the kingdom.
And they all scream the same thing
Protect Alabasta.
Stop it!
How are you so cruel?
It's heartbreaking, isn't it?
Their love for their kingdom
will be what destroys it.
Is he stupid?
Didn't he hear what I said before?
He's definitely stupid, but that's
also the reason he's our captain.
You know what?
I've had to make so many moves
to be able to get to this point.
The sabotage to inflame the citizens,
manipulating the royal army.
Do you have any idea why I'd go to
such lengths to destroy this country?
As if I'd understand anything
inside your foul mind.
You've got a pretty sharp tongue
for a princess, don't you?
Now, now, what are you
trying to do, Miss Wednesday?
Stop you.
I'm going to stop you.
There's still time.
If I can just get to
Alubarna east of here.
If I can get there before the Rebel
Army, I may be able to stop them.
I'll never give up while there's a chance.
Somehow I'm going to stop you.
Watch.
You won't get away with this!
No!
The rebel army is fast
approaching us, men!
Listen, we must protect
Alabasta with our own hands!
Do not fear death!
Fight them with everything you've got!
We must stop the rebels!
Take up intercept positions!
Alibarna's going down!
Are you okay, Koza?
You're wound.
It's nothing.
I'm fine.
Besides, if we keep riding at this
pace, we'll reach Alubarna by daybreak.
We can't stop for anything.
Just keep riding.
Yes, sir.
We attack at dawn.
You can quit fooling around now.
What a coincidence.
We were just about to head to
Alabana ourselves, Miss Wednesday.
If you'd like to come with
us, Princess, then please do.
Or...
you can try and save them.
The key...
key to this cell?
Hey! Give it!
No!
What?
A trapdoor!
It won't be too long until the rebels
and the royal forces begin their battles.
To the death even if you hurry to Alubarna
from here who knows if you'd make it
in time to stop the rebellion you need to
leave it once miss Wednesday will you do
that or try and save your friends instead
it's your choice but if you choose the
latter it doesn't help that I accidentally
drop the key into the banana gators dead
Banana gators!
What are those things?
Look out the window!
There's an alligator
growing out of that banana!
In case you haven't noticed,
that's not the only one!
It looks like we're in an aquarium.
I hope we're not the fish food.
Weird bananas.
You idiot, look closer.
They've got bananas growing out of them.
They're weird gators, not weird bananas.
What now vv what happened a big banana
Katorea just swallowed the key to your cell?
Will it go down there and
make them spit it out?
I wouldn't stand a chance
they're alpha predators!
At the top of the food
chain they're so ferocious
they even prey on sea
kings Luffy get near one!
And they'll devour you in one bite!
Sorry you might have had the
key if I hadn't accidentally
Dropped it.
And now there's no telling which
one of my pets swallowed it.
Crap!
Thanks a lot, you jerk!
Dammit, if we could just get out of here,
I could handle those overgrown reptiles.
Oh, man, you're really dumb, Zoro.
We can't get out because
the key got swallowed.
I know that, you stupid idiot!
Oh, well.
I'm sorry, but we must be going.
Time is of the essence.
Oh, and speaking of time, this room
will be destroyed in exactly one hour.
It's served me well, but
it's no longer of any use.
Soon the waters of Rainbase's
lake will fill this room,
and unless there are
fish or one of my gators,
anyone left in here won't survive.
Well, it's either one
million innocent citizens,
or a mere four pirates who have no future.
It's time to choose.
But to be honest, the odds
are quite low for both.
I hope you like gambling, Miss Wednesday,
because like they do at the tables upstairs,
you're going to have to roll the dice.
Just like I did with this country, which
was simple thanks to all the fools here.
People like those juvenile rebels,
and that old man digging in Yuba.
You don't mean that
dried up old guy, do you?
Of course, even though
everyone else has abandoned it,
that old fool keeps pecking away every
day in an oasis that's long dead.
Even as he's plagued by constant
sandstorms, he still digs away.
Shut up!
You don't know much about
sandstorms, do you, Straw Hat Luffy?
Ever wonder how one can hit
a town perfectly every time?
No, wait, you mean?
The dream of Yuba can't
be beaten by lousy sand.
I know the water will come.
You'll see.
I'll dig out the sand as
many times as it takes.
As many times as it takes.
It was you!
You did it!
Whatever it's worth, V .V.
dear, I have faith in you and his majesty.
He's a good man, a king who
would never betray his country.
I will kill you.
The room is starting to flood. Oh no.
We're all gonna drown if we
don't do something really quick.
Phoebe, help, get us out of here.
I want to live a lot
longer than just one hour.
Hey, stop freaking out.
Are you crazy, Zoro?
How can I not freak out
at a time like this?
We're all going to drown like
rats if we don't get out of here!
Don't you get it?
So it's either my kingdom or my friends.
All you've done is take, crocodile, so I
know you wouldn't give me either choice.
Even if I left for Elebarna, you'd
kill me before I ever reached it.
The only real choice,
the only way to end this nightmare is
to take out the one who started it.
Monster, you don't know a thing, not
anything, about this country's people.
It's history.
Her way of life!
Phoebe!
Get us out! You can do it! I know you can!
How, Luffy?
Ah, so you're finally starting to beg
for your life, eh, Straw Hat Luffy?
There's no shame in that.
It's only natural.
Everyone is afraid of dying.
I'm not begging!
It's just if I die, who else is
gonna be able to kick your ass?
Don't flatter yourself, you small fry.
You're a small fry who
thinks he's a big shot!
You're right, Miss Wednesday.
I would have had you killed if
you had left for the capital,
and of course I plan
on doing the same here.
That thing is so gigantic.
Phoebe!
You show that Katorea!
Are you crazy?
It's too big!
Phoebe, don't listen to this kook!
Get out of there!
But, uh, get us out, too!
She only has to be one of them!
No, look out the windows! Huh?
They're all waiting in line to eat us!
At least we won't drown like rats.
Yeah, but getting eaten by a ginormous
alligator isn't the way I want to go, either!
Kaku string!
That thing is fast! Stroke, too!
It jumped through those stone
stairs as if they were cardboard!
No! Vivi, no!
Can you hear us?
Please say something!
Tell us!
Are you alright?
Vivi, get up! Brian!
Vivi, get out of here!
It's gonna eat you!
Someone's calling.
Yes?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Yes, we can hear you.
You're a millions, right?
Hey, pal, is this thing working all right?
I've only used a transponder
snail once before.
It's working fine.
They can hear you.
Just talking to it.
What do you want?
Hurry up and state your business.
What is it?
Oh, now I know I've
heard that voice before.
Hello there, you've reached the Crab Café.
The Crab Café.
Does that ring a bell?
It should, but in case it doesn't,
maybe this will jog your memory.
Little Garden.
Yeah, hello.
You've reached the crap cafe.
Can I take your order?
You can quit fooling around.
A transponder snail?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I never used a transponder snail
once while on Little Garden.
We have four of the five Straw Hats
inside that cell based on what Mr.
Two showed us.
The only one that's left is their pet.
Do they have other members
we don't know about?
Did you hear that?
The voice was unmistakable.
Sanchi!
Shut up!
They don't know about him,
so let's keep it that way.
He was in the cabin when Mr.
Two showed up, so they never met.
He's our ace in the hole, so zip it.
Oh, that's right.
Sanchi and Chopper didn't get captured.
They're still outside.
Ah, yes.
Mind telling me who you are?
Me?
Well...
Just call me Mr. Prince.
Very well, Mr. Prince.
Mind telling me something
else, like where you are?
I'm afraid I can't say.
If I did, you'd just come a
running and get rid of me.
Even though I highly doubt you could
get rid of me, I'm not about to do so.
I'm not stupid.
I never give up information easily.
Unlike you just did, Mr. Zero.
Mr.
Prince, hurry! Come on!
If you don't hurry up, we're all
gonna end up as Katorea bait!
We're running out of time!
Get the light out, Mr.
Prince!
Go rescue us!
I'm terribly allergic to alligators!
That's my loud-mouthed crew, all right.
Thanks for letting me
know they're with you.
All I have to do is find you and I...
Say no!
Not so tough now, are you?
We've got him, sir.
Don't worry.
He won't be going anywhere in
the condition we've put him in.
Sanji...
Oh no...
So where are you? Speak up?
I'm at the front of the casino with
the Katorea on top and rain base.
Rain dinners!
If he's not dead, he's gonna wish he was!
Cause I'm gonna kill
him next time I see him!
No, Sanji!
That poor guy!
Stay right there.
Well, we shouldn't leave the man waiting.
Is this wise?
The millions still don't know the
actual identity of their boss.
Aside from the number agents, no
one knows who you and I truly are.
Everyone thinks I'm a local
hero who also owns this casino.
There's nothing suspicious
about a proprietor going
to see what happened in
front of this building.
Our secret will be safe.
Baby!
Hey, what are you doing?
We still have time before this
room fills completely with water.
I'm going outside to help you know who.
Gotcha.
There's no way he kicked
the bucket, not that guy.
If you can get him free, then
I'm sure he can get us free.
And Chopper's out there too,
so we might actually have a
chance of getting out of here.
Baby, look out!
I've had enough of your nonsense.
Since you care for your friends that much,
Miss Wednesday, you can
just die here with them.
Which, thanks to the rising
water and my hungry pets outside,
should occur very, very soon.
Now, if you'll excuse
me, I'm going to drag Mr.
Prince back here to join you.
I hope you don't mind corpses.
Crocodile!
Oh, my. Mr. Crocodile, sir.
Have you heard what's
happening in Nanohana?
Hmm. Yes. Tragic. The whole town.
No, the whole country is in an uproar.
Everyone's talking about it.
It appears the royal army and the rebel
army, they're finally about to clash.
Oh, well.
I'm not surprised the king does
let pirates attack the cities.
I always thought something like this might
happen if Cobra kept
letting this country suffer.
Hey, look over there!
It's him!
Crocodile! I love him! Wow!
A public appearance in the casino!
Seems you're as popular as ever.
Daisy!
They've been there for me all this time.
You've never let me down,
so I do not let them down.
And I won't let them die like this.
All right, she got away.
Things have just gone from bad to worse.
And the rain is blowing!
We don't even have an hour left!
We'll be lucky if we have 20 minutes!
Vivi! Are you okay?
I'm fine!
I'm going to get help, so just hold on!
I will get you out of there!
I'm not going to abandon
any of you, I promise!
I'll be right back with help, okay?
Okay!
You can do it, Vivi!
What the hell is this?
These were the remaining
millions we had in town.
If you include those that
Pell the Falcon took down,
every last one of them
have been wiped out.
Hey, who did this? Tell me.
A guy.
He was called Mr. Prince.
But I thought you idiots caught him.
So where the hell did he go?
He headed toward the south part of town.
He just left.
South?
I see.
Run, then.
Run all you want, but you can't escape me.
You could forget him.
Oh, no.
I've always killed those
foolish enough to cross me.
And that's not a habit
I'm quitting anytime soon!
Oh, is that a crazy wipe?
I'm not sure.
But it caused the bridge
to the casino to collapse.
The whole thing's gone.
What?
You mean we're stranded in here?
Now I can't gamble.
Hey, how do we get out of here?
Aren't there any boats?
What happened?
The bridge collapsed!
What? Oh, no.
The bridge is out.
That means I'm locked in.
I didn't do it to keep you in.
I did it to keep those Baroque
works creeps out, gorgeous.
It's one part of the plan you see.
The other part is chopper running
around town is a decoy we're
going to stop the civil war that's
about to erupt in this country!
We've got to hurry so?
Think you can tell me where our
friends are at well princess?